so one of the nice things about hych and
our little search Community is that we
have people coming back uh regular
visitors to to hch or even regular
presenters uh so we can actually track
their search progress and see how they
go um one of them is Julian from wpop
wopop is the largest Spanish ctoc
Marketplace and he's talking about how
precision and recall relate to actual
business metrics in their experience and
J the stage is yours thank
you all right thank you Matias and yes
I'm Julian French but I live in
Barcelona so uh super happy to be here I
hope you will you will enjoy I it will
not be super technical uh the idea is
that you get some intuition about what
we are doing and also
probably uh it will trigger some
discussions that's a little bit the goal
I will not talk about llms or rag or
anything like this I hope uh you will
still for example I would ask you to
wear your user hat no think as if you
were a user not really an engineer or
anything like that okay so uh Maas
already introduced wapop so we are a
leader in secondhand and unique Goods
Marketplace in Spain also in Italy in
Portugal and actually search is a very
challenging topic for secondhand
marketplaces we have very specific
challenges uh in this area and if you
are interested we can discuss it later
as
well I will not spend too much time on
this actually what I will present here
is not exactly something we have done
specifically at wapop
it's not a project that we have been
doing or anything like this and
everything does not relate 100% to wapop
okay so take it like a general
discussion let's start by a very simple
example okay I'm looking for a chair
very very simple maybe today we need a
few more actually for the conference so
we can buy on on
wapop um I'm looking for chairs and we
have this set of results
uh obviously there are some results that
look okay the ones in the Middle look
like accessories not so good and the one
on the right hand side look more like
desks probably they sell the desks with
the chairs that's why they are matched
but doesn't seem so so good now if you
you are a user you are not like an
engineer or anything like this do you
think this result is good for for you
you can raise your hand if you think
it's good
wow and if we only look at the two first
results is it good for you yeah a little
bit better now if you look at you're not
a user you're the CEO or I don't know
CTO maybe as
well uh what do you think is it good or
not so good yeah it's maybe a little bit
better especially if there are some of
those ads that are promoting like this
morning we have seen with the friends
from o some of the ads usually are
promoted for different reasons and you
want to give more visibility to Those
ads and maybe that's what's happening to
those desks here they are here because
of they are promoted or not I don't
know okay so um overall I guess you all
know what precision and recall is we
will uh talk about it a bit later as
well it's a very old problem but it's
still very important today and
especially in those two context
e-commerce and marketplaces but not only
can also apply to other places so as
similar to like in many social media
feeds uh many search results Pages look
like infinite Scrolls no you you can you
start searching you see results and you
keep scrolling scrolling scrolling you
can scroll forever you will always see
results no and this is why no when you
think about it the first part usually
it's very precise very precise oriented
but when you keep scrolling down you
will end up seeing random results very
likely and this is more what we call
here the recall part now
and why do we want to do this now of
course there is like many companies want
to to Foster discovery of the users to
keep them engaged and so that they keep
scrolling in order to maybe discover
some interesting results at some point
and the second aspect is that uh many
companies like like us we want to avoid
zero or very few results because it
gives a very for experience probably the
worst thing you can show to the user is
an empty screen page so we I think we we
all know this and also we have seen this
a lot uh during today's
talk uh now we often frame search as to
phases candidate retrieval and then we
have a layers of rankings and uh on top
of it and if we want to fit the ranking
with the right items usually what we do
is we are we have a candidate for trial
phase that is kind of relaxed no we we
want to make sure we return all the
possibly relevant items to R rankers and
this leads as well to now having a huge
list of results that we want to
rank the problem I think we we all know
it uh many users actually scroll a lot
and uh I don't know maybe you don't have
access to this data but we look when you
look at it you might be surprised they
do scroll a lot in the search results
and so what happens is that obviously
they they end up seeing results that are
not relevant for them and another
classical problem of of search is when
they start changing the sort order from
relevance to something else bam it's
it's you start to to really show
completely random
stuff and this happens when you really
aggressively expand
recall and of course now in more modern
times uh with the Vector search or dense
retrieval what happens is the game has
changed completely with respect to
recall we are those techniques are super
good at recall and maybe sometimes too
good no you can always scroll the same
way as we said before and for example in
previous talk now that's what happened
you you don't know where to cut because
you can always keep retrieving uh
results so we will look at at those
things uh from two perspective now user
perspective and more prec the user
perception and business
metrics so let's go back to very simple
um Notions here precision and recall we
we have seen it before and then we will
present what we call user experience
metric and in the second phase business
metric so precision and recall no need
to go too much into detail here
Precision is the percentage of return
return items that are relevant and
recall is percentage of relevant items
that are returned and we know that they
are
contradictory uh nothing new here okay
so those ones are I forget for
now user experience metrics actually
it's something
that maybe it's not covered so much in
in the search Community we talk a lot
about inds ctrs and so on but not
really uh looking at user satisfaction
what do the users think about our search
and why is it important well actually
the search experience is way more than
just looking at a list of results and
and making sure that the order is the
right one no uh we have to take into
account the whole experience so it it
includes uh for example
suggestions uh all the different tools
you have uh you you bring to your users
to refine the queries like filters you
can change the sort order as you can see
here and and of course the for example
spell checker is another classical thing
that you have to take into account so
those user experience metrics they
measure satisfaction of the users it's a
very broad topic but actually there is
uh a lot of uh formal Frameworks behind
this no all these ux uh Frameworks that
um have been sted for a long time they
used a lot in different companies and we
want to see how it matches with our SE
uh practice so here I will just consider
one very simple example which
is this pyramid of user needs no it
tries to model what is the the feeling
of the users depending on the maturity
of your of your product no on the base
of the pyramid you have functional it
means your product is I mean it's
functional it works nothing more nothing
less it's not broken uh it works that's
the the basic no the found of of your
product on top of it you have re
reliable it means uh it works but also
it's stable over time latency is
acceptable uh it will not crash every
every two weeks and sometimes I mean it
it sounds like super easy but actually
there are lots of technical challenges
here to make this
possible the next layer is called usable
here and so it means you provide all the
tools that the user needs to satisfy the
need now for example what we said before
like good suggestion filters save
searches is another U aspect of it so we
we are not really talking here about the
the relevancy of the search itself no
it's more what's what's uh on top of it
and then at the top of the pyamid you
have like you know it's more
like purely delightful you you provide a
very nice experience to the users you
have this wow this product is so cool
it's fantastic and so this is really the
the end goal of user experience but what
happens to search and again here I don't
want to generalize it's not always the
case but overall search is a very common
feature in many webs or e-commerce
marketplaces H users they know how to
use search it's not like it's not new
know they there's a a search box they
type into it and they know how it works
and so what happens is
usually for search the users they don't
have necessarily the need of a
delightful experience they just want
search to work as expected and to work
well and that's very important because
it will conditionally bit the the
feedback that you get from your users
and you will see it in a second so
that's what I've written here now the
the users usually expect reliable
accurate results whatever that means and
not necessarily delightful experiences
how do you collect those um ux metrics
there are lots of ways you can do it
here are it's just a little uh extract
of it you can send surveys to your users
you ask questions like are the search
results relevant and they will rate yes
no um so
so and you can ask a lot of question
actually and you can out of this you can
extract some some metrics that will tell
you how satisfies are your user by your
search you can conduct user interviews
uh it's super insightful actually if you
have never done this I encourage you to
do it you sit down with some users and
you you see how the users are
interacting with the search and I'm sure
you will be super
surprised I mean we did the the exercise
and it's like wow they are not using
search at all the way we we are thinking
it's very different so but problem of
user interviews is that it doesn't scale
it's very biased as well depends on the
user you select but still I think it's
more like from an inside perspective
that you you can use
this uh I think you cannot read it very
well here uh you can also add feedback
components in your search results and
asking your user do you like it do you
like it blah blah blah you can also
input some very input uh text that the
user can fit in and then you post
analyze it and it brings a lot of
insights as well and finally you can
check your app previews again it's very
biased but always super insightful and
it's it's almost clear they will
complain about search they always
complain about search even if you have
the best search on Earth they will
complain about search that's super fun I
it's not fun but it's the
reality um here I mean it's a super
simple slide but actually I think it's
one of the most
important uh what we have seen here know
what the user tell you when you ask
those questions is what they feel it's a
perception of the
user but it might not be the same as the
utility for the user for example in the
end the users in in wapop they use wapop
for buying things not for seeing good
results it's very different and
sometimes we have this bias here like
user perception is one thing and user
utility is another thing we will come to
it in a few slides uh but keep in mind
these different
here so business metric what I call
business business metric here is
something I guess we are more used uh to
in this audience like no we have talked
a lot today about n dcgs but here I mean
also everything related to conversions
no search conversions it can be also
user engagement retention everything
related to zero results and of course
everything related directly to revenue
can be also good business metrics I will
not extend a lot because I think you all
know I think you you use them on a daily
basis so now we will go through two
examples we will stay at a very
intuitive level I will not go into into
uh more details but I I would like just
you to understand more or less the the
perception that we have here so the
example is as follows I'm searching for
ski boots and what happens I again I
have six results
but two of the results are like nonsense
what we don't know why there's those two
two results here no the third one and
the fifth one here the other ones
without more context they look
okay maybe they are not because maybe
the price is super expensive but at
least they they look okay okay like this
so first we we we see it from user
perspective so what happens when you see
this and you can ask the users they will
tell you your search is broken it
doesn't work there is something wrong
it's a bug or you know they don't
understand that maybe search is just an
algorithm behind that will mat things
they don't understand this and so for
from a user perspective this is a very
bad result
and now if you look at it from a
business perspective okay those are just
two bad results but doesn't really
matter no they will not be clicked and
that's it no it's not a big drama no um
it's almost similar to having skib boots
that will not be clicked you know it's
very it's not a big
deal now I take the opposite
example which is I still have my query
ski boots and I return two but I know
that in in my catalog I had a lot more
skib boots that could have been relevant
but for whatever reason they will not
return to the to the to the user so what
happens now I still look at this from
user perspective
well I see two pair of Hots it's good
and so there is no impact on the user
because the user cannot know that there
were other Goods available in the
catalog so it's in the worst case maybe
the user will think that the catalog is
poor or the application is I mean there
are not enough sellers to sell boots but
the user will never complain about this
search result is super precise fantastic
however from a business perspective here
this recall issue is can be dramatic
because depending on the number of boots
that you have failed too
much um if you look at your metrics it
of course they can be super uh super
impacted so you you you have a big uh
opportunity loss
here so as I said it's just from purely
intuitive level what we see is but
actually in in practice it will it works
very well if you disagree with this we
can discuss it later no problem but
overall what happens is user perception
of search is highly cor to precision and
the business metrics highly cor to
recall that you have seen before and
exactly in the same way uh we have this
contradiction between the two it's a
little bit counterintuitive because for
example we all use n DC because it's
supposed to be super correlated with
user experience as well so something
seems to be broken here and and as like
an open controversial question um we can
wonder if for example business metrics
are more correlated to the utility that
I discussed before uh it's not super
clear but uh it could be the
case so
now two extreme
cases and I've seen this a lot in
different companies no one
case uh your team is completely obsessed
in optimizing ndgs rankings conversion
rates and you are using all the most
fancy ml models around and it's the only
thing that your team is doing very
likely uh you would benefit from just
forgetting this about for a moment you
take your user hat and you see maybe you
you have something very basic broken in
your search experience check check your
favorite searches your I don't know your
suggestor maybe is is not as good as it
should be and maybe this will bring a
lot more value than just keeping
iterating small decimals of NS on your
on your search the it's an extreme case
I know we most of us we are not like
this second case is the opposite like
there are teams that are super user
Centric only looking at with Obsession
at the surveys MPS scores and app
previews and very likely they are
tending towards optimizing too much for
precision
and it's almost sure that they are
losing a big Opportunity by not checking
Rec in those cases so again I'm
generalizing it's not always like this
but I think it it happens in many
cases okay now from the people here who
is like on the tech side of search like
Engineers data
scientists ml scientist
yeah quite quite a lot and how many are
more on the product side I don't know
product managers
designers a bit less so you will tell
you will tell me if this applies to you
or not I'm not sure so you usually what
happens is that the the first case that
I explained here uh we see a lot of
teams heavily relying on search
Engineers ml all those kind of more Tech
profiles they tend to focus a lot more
on those aspects of purely uh NDC GS and
so
on and the teams that are more Centric
like with a lot of weight on the product
management side designer you ux
researchers usually they see it very
differently they don't care about indic
at all and you can say that you want to
use I don't know a fancy
algorithm why because your search is
broken doesn't really make sense no so
overall I think we the the overall
search Community will gain a lot if we
manage to close this gap between the two
views um let me check my time okay we
will illustrate a little bit this
difference
uh on the the the query
specificity example here okay and we
will see cases where expanding too much
on recall can also hurt a lot the user I
take an example here which is very basic
I have a query which is Fender uh so
it's a music
brand and at this stage we don't know
more like it can be anything it can be a
guitar it can be an amplifier it can be
anything of this brand and you see there
there are quite a lot of
results now if I keep typing I enter
faster which is the the type of guitar
so now we know it's a guitar so when you
do this
you see there are less results no it's
pretty intuitive and if I keep writing I
get to a point where I have very few
results and this is this behavior when
the query specificity
increases um and you see less and less
and less results it's something very
intuitive for the users they are
expecting this from the search engine
they are not expecting to see the same
number of results when you increase the
the specificity of the query and now in
many many places you see this behavior
is broken you will see always the same
number of results no matter what is the
the query
specificity no so like the the intuition
of the user is when you increase
specificity which is this axis here you
should see a decrease on number of
results and pretty quickly you will get
to a point where you have zero results
which is uh logical I would say the big
problem here is and we all know it when
you get to this phase where you have
zero or very few results it's not good
for the for the users and it's not good
for the business neither so this is the
little icon we show to our users when
there is no results and now we one of
goal is to avoid this now it's very bad
for the
users
so actually there are two reasons for
having zero results no one is you don't
have any res any relevant results in
your catalog in this case it's very good
to say to your user okay I don't have
any relevant result for you it's
transparency know and actually I think
Eric P gave a talk on this I don't know
when one year ago also so some of you I
think know know this guy and so this is
one one reason for not getting relevant
result the second reason for getting
zero result is uh you have actually in
your catalog relevant results but
something went wrong in the matching
phase in the retrieval phase and you
could not match uh you could you could
not find those items no in this case of
course you need to improve your recal
but not at all
cost actually something
interesting uh in real life is that in
the end if you think about it the
probability of a bad matching happening
when the query specificity increases
uh is also increasing because no the
more words you have the more probability
you have of having typos synonyms in
between that can prevent the matching
vocabulary gap of course over
specification as well now users type
writing words that are not so useful but
they will kill the matching and so this
happens a lot now if you look at it from
a little bit more Modern Eyes now for
example if you do a pure old cool
keyword matching with an end you will
see this behavior that the users are
expecting like the more
words the less results it's like what
you it's what you get in common search
engines now if if you do some Vector
search assuming you will retrieve the
top K you will get K all the time
doesn't really matter how many terms or
specificity you have and so basically
the user intuition is broken here and
even if you go for other types
of of techniques like Spate for example
not this Spar Square expansion it can
even be worse like the more words you
add the bigger is your expansion and the
more results you will get when you do
the dot product
so what happens is that usually this
Zone here is fantastic for the business
because you you you manage to return a
lot of content to the users and very
likely they met will go up but because
you completely break the intuition for
the user on this topic this is not so
good for the user in the end so you want
to be if you want to go in this space
you need to do something for your users
because otherwise on the long term you
you might have some some issues like
users might not be retained or might go
to another app for example even if again
in terms of ncgs and so on maybe this is
fantastic
so here what what we see now it's
aggressively improving recall for
specific
queries it's true that it will help you
tackle the zero or few results problem
and very likely it will be good for your
business metrics but you should not
forget about this user
perception
aspect so the question is how can we be
in this space here but taking into
account what the user expects no so here
again it's not really specific to
wup and I'm sure you will have better
solution than this but I would just
provide some guidance on things we can
do and probably things that some of you
are already doing uh so an an obvious
thing I guess probably if you are using
like semantic search Vector search or
whatever probably you are already doing
things like this no uh which is post
filtering uh because your you know your
retrieval can go a little bit crazy so
at least if you make sure you post
filter some of the results to make sure
I don't know for example you are in the
right category you will probably limit
the risk of having very bad
results so that's what we call here
filtering out
defects uh so this is overall not to
limit those kind of examples but it will
not help with the query specificity
example I shown before
the second option is
actually because we are always talking
about search results but you can also
change the UI of your search and it's
not so hard if you think about it it's
it's not so hard so what about instead
of having one infinite fit of results
you can just split into two parts one
super super focused on precision and the
other ones you can call it like a more
recall part part no recall section in
this case uh it can be good because for
example in the first section I can show
my exact matchings matches which is
basically the ones I am almost 100% sure
they correspond to the intent of the
user in my case of before I would show
my the only exact guitar that the user
is looking for and then in the other
section I can show basically what I want
doesn't really matter I can promote a
lot if I want the
promoted items from for the business and
I I can
also avoid zero results because maybe
there is not exactly this model here I
can relax a little bit I can use the the
techniques that Renee shared last year
for
example
and so it can also be a very good
strategic strategic change no because
you you have very little risk on the
second section so it it sounds like a
good compromise however of course it
comes also with some
drawbacks you add some complexity into
it you have to manage now two set of
results so in terms of logging also if
you want to collect the feedbacks of the
users it might not be so so easy as
before and also the the question of
always no where where do you cut now how
do you decide that this one should be in
the first section and this one in the
second one uh the this depends a lot on
on on your business it's not so so easy
but at least you have decoupled the two
things and from a user perspective it's
more
intuitive okay and also very
important in the lights of what we have
seen just before um if you think about
it we are always optimizing things for
the average user because we are we are
taking averages everywhere in n thises
in all the metrics but in the end an
average user does not is they are al
they are very different the users and
for example we see it in in WAP now
there are users that clearly prefer
Simplicity of the search box they type
everything in the search box and they
start to write in natural language
because now it's more normal even the
price filter they would write uh looking
for chairs
under2 and there are some users and
there will always be users that prefer
the hardcoree
hardcore filter experience and you need
to provide filters so they would write
write chair and you you need to provide
filters that make sense like in price in
seller rating or
whatever so and overall when you listen
to your users in those interviews or
whatever you will see that those kind of
users are still very important because
maybe also those are core users that use
your app since a lot of time and they
are not taking
changes in your product in in a very
positive way so you don't want to lose
them and and there are very simple
things you can do and you should not
forget about those things it's very easy
to enable in your UI the the user to to
search on title only or exact matches
you know very basic things that you had
like 20 years ago uh pretty easy to
implement but it can bring a lot of
value to your to your
users I've seen I've seen
your some takeaways
so overall when you build the search
system uh it's not all about ncgs and so
on you you have to take into account
business metrics but also the user
perception
metrics uh again sit down with your
users and talk to them it's very
insightful overall and if you disagree
or if you have different experience we
can discuss it later but overall
business metrics they are more related
to recall and user perception and I
insist it's perception of the user it's
more related to Precision so it's kind
of the same old tradeoff that we we have
always uh had
inert an important point that we have
briefly discussed is that user
perception that you collect via those
metrics in the end it's not the same as
user utility and here uh again I think
we we should open a discussion maybe
it's uh the same but maybe it's not and
of course you should not blind blindly
trust your business metric but also not
blindly trust your user perception
metric the two are kind of flowed and in
the end it's very I think it's it's
better to to look at them holistically
and the the two at the same
time we know in the case of query
specificity we have seen other there in
the end there there are simple ways you
can optimize recall without impacting
precision too much at least without
compromising the
experience uh and what I mean there are
other techniques than the one we have
seen here but sometimes it's very it's
very easy and it's even easier to do
those kind of things than trying to
complexify too much your ranking
algorithm to take multiobjectives or
whatever now sometime we it's better to
take like a step back and think about
the the overall experience
and of course for example at some point
depending on the maturity of your
product um you might want to decide to
change the UI and add sections for
example but maybe in few years from now
the maturity of your product has changed
and you want to move back to one single
section it it really depend on on the
maturity of your of your product and
also on on business
priorities and finally for those two
things non business metrics and for user
metrics as well it's very important to
keep experimenting measuring it's like
everything is about feedback loops now
as we have seen this morning so it's we
I think we all know it
for uh the the models we use we want to
do a testings and so on but it's also
true for the user perception metric you
want to set up a system where you can
you can track them and
also uh make sure you are not degrading
through time and it's it's interesting
here we have discussed about about those
user perception metric and could be
interesting to discuss if they are
somehow linked to the Ubi metrics we
have discussed this morning it's not
exactly the same thing but maybe there
are ways to to log those as well uh in a
similar
framework okay and I think that's all
gracias
and thank you thank you julan do we have
any questions here in the
audience uh thanks for the talk I was
wondering how do you advise Engineers to
take on the users hat do you think they
should just look at the results from a
users's perspective or should get
involved in the user interviews or stuff
like that yeah it's it's a very good
question actually that's what we we
invite them directly to assist to those
interviews and usually that's what
happens is that they are surprised
because the the users are not behaving
as expected and also because Engineers
they are quite used to to metrics to
those n DCS and so on so also checking
more like qu on a quarterly basis on
those surveys uh even looking at the the
reviews and so on is a little bit the
same no it's
like it tells a lot about your search so
yeah and it's not it's not too hard in
the end and usually it comes from it's
it's driven by ux researchers or product
managers um so usually we we need those
profiles to encourage search Engineers
to to look at this and I would say the
other way around is true as well
like quite often ux researcher designers
and so on they only look at user metrics
but when when you talk about n dcgs you
they think that you are just crazy
optimizing but so yeah it's like both
sides thank you thanks I'll take that
home thank you we have one question
online it's a bit longer I try to um
interpret or paraphrase so the question
is whether we can use explicit user
feedback like disliking a certain search
result and use that as kind of a
feedback loop to yeah use more
personalized uh models that optimize or
find a different balance between
position and recall um like
reinforcement learning for human
feedback is that something that would
improve the situation in your opinion or
is that a viable approach I think it's a
great question I think usually what
happens is that it might not be so
scalable because if you need you need to
collect those feedbacks and users will
will not spend a lot of time giving
feedback so I think it's a very it's a
very useful uh signal you can use you
can even use it to train your models and
so on or to monitor I think the
difficulty here is to have really a
scalable solution that you can collect
enough of those feedbacks so up to
getting to a point where you can
personalize it yeah maybe because if a
user gives you clear uh Insight that
something is wrong you can you can
easily introduce it in your personalized
experience but
overall I think the at least the way we
do it it's not really scalable because
also we we don't provide like a way to
give feedback on each single result no
it's more every x positions we show like
a small box to request feedback so I
think the the what is proposing in in
the question is more having a specific
button
somewhere to get the
feedback than another
question hi uh thanks a lot um yeah I
really like the presentation I really
agree with the idea that you know user
experience has to be really important in
this stuff my question is or my
understanding of like a lot of search
applications is that things like recall
are kind of unknowable because a lot of
the time you don't actually know what
the true positives are that you're
searching for right so how do you get
around that or what sort of metrics are
you actually using to approximate recoil
yeah can you please repeat the I I
couldn't hear the second part of your if
you have a situation where you don't
actually know what the most relevant
results are for a query how do you
calculate
recall yeah no it's a good question
actually the example I is pretty easy
because um even if you look you think
about it as exact match or exact term
match then you know where to stop no but
in most of the cases I agree with you
it's complex you could have like a no
actually what what we have quite often
is the the relevance the relevance does
not only depend on the semantic
relevance there is many things happening
uh no other factors that are also
important so at least in marketplaces
what happens sometimes is that you you
can have a dedicated model only for
purely semantic relevance on top of it
and then you can use it to decide if
it's good enough for uh the the first
part or not but it's very specific to
secondhand C2C marketplaces it might not
work in other other places but I agree
with you it's that's the the old
challenge of this you don't know where
to to stop yeah
okay any more
questions uh muchas gracias for a nice
presentation uh I wanted to ask you
mentioned a bunch of uh very uh
pragmatic practical tools to understand
what your users doing better have you
ever used
session recordings as a way to observe
what users are doing when you are really
not watching like I mean real
recordings like video you mean
recordings of the users of the session
yeah yeah that's what I meant by user
interviews so we see the user
directly no no not user interviews but
uh like uh getting um users to accept uh
some uh parameters and just tools that
requ record live sessions and you can
review later just screen recording no
it's a it's a good point now we at least
on my experience we have not used this
but I can also ask to our ux researcher
if it's something we can we can use it's
a good question when we can maybe talk
about it later I would love to I would
love to thank
you yeah I have a question about the
generalizability about the assumption
that um Precision correlates with uh the
user perception so I definitely
subscribe to it in
e-commerce uh maybe less so in B2B where
it's a lot about known item and if I
can't find this item that I know must be
there there might be more about recall
and then there might be more
recall dependent domains like let's say
legal search or
something so I don't know maybe there's
always this element of trust which goes
with position
or maybe there's a recall aspect in
other domains so what's your take on
that it's a very good question actually
that's also that why I wanted to trigger
is those kind of discussions because at
least in in Market in Marketplace it's
pretty obvious that if if you look at
the complaints of the users it's like
99% of the cases that search is not
relevant it's it's really about lack of
precision of the sh but if you look at
then how the the business metric
correlate with your changes it's like
wow wow it's no no it's not Precision
the problem it's a recall problem that
we have but I agree with you that it
might not apply in other fields and even
in e-commerce it's true that maybe it's
not 100% true so all of this has to be
taken with it's more like aspirational
and but we can yeah we can again we can
discuss it later it's interesting and I
would be super happy to
hear uh what what you think about all
this
okay let's thank Julian again for this
great talk